eastwestcenter.org 2018-06-29

# Privacy Statement | East-West Center | www.eastwestcenter.org

The East-West Center wants you to enjoy your visit to www.eastwestcenter.org. The East-West Center takes your on-line privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our on-line Privacy Statement and Policy. By visiting this website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement and Policy.

I. **What this Privacy Statement and Policy Covers**

 This Privacy Statement and Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that the East-West Center and its affiliate organizations collect when you are on the www.eastwestcenter.org website. This policy does not apply to: (1) the practices of companies that the East-West Center does not own or control; (2) people that the East-West Center does not employ or manage; (3) websites that you link to through the www.eastwestcenter.org website; and (4) activities by the East-West Center and its affiliates outside of the on-line context.

 II. **Information Collection**

 A. **Information That You Provide to Us**

 The East-West Center collects and maintains personally identifiable information that you provide to us when you: (1) subscribe to East-West Center email updates; (2) complete an on-line registration form for East-West Center programs or seminars; (3) buy products on-line at our East-West Center site; and (4) submit a question or comment by completing a form on the East-West Center site. When you register with www.eastwestcenter.org, we may ask for your name, mailing address, zip code, telephone number and/or email address. When you buy an East-West Center product or service, we may also ask for a credit card number.

 B. **Information That We Collect Automatically**

 We collect certain types of information automatically whenever you access and use our website. Examples of the information we collect automatically include: (1) the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; (2) the browser software you are using; (3) your operating system; and (4) the date and time you access our website. This information is not cross-referenced with registrant names or any other registrant information and therefore is not personally identifiable. This information is used solely for statistical purposes and to ensure that you are able to access the website properly on your computer.

 C. **Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites. 

Our cookies help us:

  * Make our website work as you'd expect
  * Improve the speed/security of the site
  * Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook

 D. **Google Analytics and AddThis**

 This website uses _Google Analytics_ , a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics maintains their own privacy policy located [here](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). This website also uses _AddThis.com_ 's services for social sharing of web content. Addthis.com's privacy statement is located [here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy). Occasionally, the East-West Center website may embed content from other websites (such as videos from YouTube.com or Vimeo.com). Please refer to those separate companies for their specific privacy policies.

 III. **Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

 The East-West Center uses your personal information for three general purposes: 

1) to fulfill your requests for products, services and information,  
2) to respond to your inquiries, and  
3) to contact you about new products and services.

 IV. **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

 The East-West Center may share your personally identifiable information with direct affiliates, including, but not limited to, the East-West Center Foundation and the East-West Center Association. Neither the East-West Center nor its affiliates will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your permission.

 Please be advised that the East-West Center reserves the right to disclose any personal information about you without your prior consent if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with valid legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; (2) protect our rights or property; (3) prevent harm to you or others.

 V. **Editing Your Personal Information**

You have the ability to edit personal information you provide to us by emailing us at [ webhelp@eastwestcenter.org](mailto:webhelp@eastwestcenter.org). You can also find out what personal information we have on record for you by emailing us at [ webhelp@eastwestcenter.org](mailto:webhelp@eastwestcenter.org).

 VI. **Your Ability to "Opt-out" of Receiving Future Communications from Us**

You may request that we not email and/or mail you information regarding new products, services and/or any other marketing material, or that the East-West Center discontinue emailing updates to you by contacting us at [ webhelp@eastwestcenter.org](mailto:webhelp@eastwestcenter.org).

 VII. **Security**

 In order to protect against the improper disclosure of your personal information, only authorized employees with passwords are permitted access to the personal information that you provide to us. To further protect your personal information, we also maintain online safeguards. We use industry-standard security technologies, including SSL-encryption.

 The East-West Center strives to protect the transmission of all information visitors submit. No transmission of data is completely secure, however, so submissions are at the visitor's risk. The East-West Center shall not be liable under any circumstances for damages resulting from use of information collected from visitors to the site.

 VIII. **Website Visitors Outside of the United States**

 This Privacy Statement and Policy was drafted to comply with United States law. If you’re outside of the United States, the laws of your country regarding privacy might be different from those of the United States, and we can provide no assurances that our Policy and practices conform to the laws of all countries. You should consult an appropriate professional in your country if you wish to know whether our Policy and practices conform to the laws that protect privacy in your country.

IX. **Changes to This Privacy Statement and Policy**

The East-West Center may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. Please note that your continued use of this website means that you accept the amendments to this Privacy Statement and Policy.

 X. **Violations of This Privacy Statement and Policy**

 If at any time you believe that the East-West Center has not adhered to the principles in this Privacy Statement and Policy, please notify us by e-mail at [ webhelp@eastwestcenter.org](mailto:webhelp@eastwestcenter.org)and we will work to promptly correct the problem.

 XI. **Questions or Suggestions**

 If you have questions or suggestions please email us at [ webhelp@eastwestcenter.org](mailto:webhelp@eastwestcenter.org) , or visit the  Web Helppage.

 ** A note about links to third party websites**

For your convenience, this website may contain links to other websites  operated by third parties ("third party websites"). In making these hyperlinks available, the Center is not endorsing those third-party websites, their content, products or services they offer, nor the owners of these third party websites. It is your responsibility to ensure that you obtain all information relevant to making a decision and that you read the privacy and security policy on those third-party websites. We have no control over such third-party websites and will not be liable for any loss or damage you suffer, whether directly or indirectly, as a result of your use of third party websites. You agree that where you access third party websites, you do so entirely at your own risk.

© 5/14/2018 East-West Center. All Rights Reserved.
